<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Prana</string>
    <string name="title_lifestyle">Lifestyle</string>
    <string name="title_habit">Habit Tracker</string>
    <string name="title_remedies">Remedies</string>

    <!--Onboarding Screen-->
    <string name="heading_onboarding_importance">Importance of Ayurvedic lifestyle</string>
    <string name="content_onboarding_importance">Ayurveda is often called the “Mother of All Healing.” It enables one to understand how to make lifestyle changes to create the balance of body, mind and consciousness.</string>
    <string name="heading_onboarding_how_to_build">How to build your Ayurvedic lifestyle</string>
    <string name="content_onboarding_how_to_build">This app will teach and guide you through the right equation for a healthy Ayurvedic lifestyle.</string>
    <string name="heading_onboarding_habit_tracker">A habit tracker</string>
    <string name="content_onboarding_habit_tracker">Along with information on Ayurvedic lifestyle this app will also help you maintain a balanced lifestyle with a habit tracker.</string>
    <string name="heading_onboarding_home_remedies">Home remedies</string>
    <string name="content_onboarding_home_remedies">Learn how to use the best ingredients from home to stay healthy. These home remedies with “0” side effects will help with different health conditions.</string>
    <string name="terms_and_conditions_disclaimer">This app shows information from certified Ayurvedic professional. Any person with serious health conditions or any allergies should consult an Ayurvedic professional prior to taking any advice. We are not responsible for any events of illness occured. </string>

    <!--Buttons-->
    <string name="text_continue">Continue</string>
    <string name="text_skip">Skip</string>
    <string name="title_activity_scrolling">ScrollingActivity</string>
    <string name="large_text">
        "Ayurveda has a set of simple rules to help you ensure that you make the most of your daily meals. With guidelines for what to eat, how much to eat, and how to eat, your meals can be your best medicine.\n"

    </string>

    <string name="large_text2">

        \nAyurveda has long used diet as a principal means of creating health within the body and mind. Hundreds of years before Hippocrates instructed, “Let food be thy medicine,” Ayurveda defined principles for making that advice practical. Food selection, meal timing, and state of awareness during meal either increases (vitality) or ama (toxicity). The following 6 rules will serve as a guide to create health, vitality, and energy through food.
\n\n<b>1. Select Foods for Your Dosha Type</b>\n\n
One’s current doshic imbalance, known as vikruiti, is a combination of two elements that are heightened within the physiology. By eating foods that decrease the heightened elements, harmony can be restored with the body.
\n\n<b>Vata Dosha:</b> Persons with excess Vata energy will restore balance through foods that are warm (in terms of both temperature and spice), hydrating (such as soups and stews), full of healthy fats (like olive oil, ghee, organic cream, and avocados), and grounding (think dense, healthy comfort foods).
\n\n<b>Pitta Dosha:</b> Eating foods that are cool (especially in terms of internal cooling such as is seen with peppermint, cucumber, cilantro, and parsley), astringent (beans, legumes, pomegranate, and green tea), substantial, and mild will minimize the aggravation of the Pitta.
\n\n<b>Kapha Dosha:</b> Eating foods that are light, warm, dry (like beans and popcorn) and rough (think “roughage” such as vegetables) will have Kapha back in balance in no time.
\n\n<b>2. Eliminate Snacks</b>\n\n
According to Ayurvedic principles, there are three stages of digestion that must be completed after a meal. In the first hour after a meal, the Kapha energies are dominant. The body may feel full, heavy, and sedate. Two to four hours after a meal the elements of Pitta govern digestion. During this time, hydrochloric acid increases, internal heat rises, and the meal is transformed into sustenance for the body. Four to five hours after a meal the Vata energies rise. It is during this time that lightness and space return and appetite increases. Interruption of the digestive cycle with more food leads to incomplete digestion.
\n\n<b>3. Eat Until Satisfied, Not Full</b>\n\n
Aside from the obvious consequence of weight gain, overeating increases free radical production in the body, which in turn speeds the aging process. By setting down the fork when you are satisfied, but not stuffed, you avoid overeating and the body receives the nourishment that it needs without the added burden of digesting, and oftentimes storing, unnecessary calories.
\n\n<b>4. Consume Whole, Fresh Foods</b>\n\n
According to the Ayurveda diet, the best way to increase ojas, the supplier of life force in the body, is to increase prana. Foods with abundant prana come straight from the Earth. The moment food is picked, its prana begins slowly diminishing. Therefore, eating foods that are as fresh as possible will increase prana more readily than eating the same foods further from their harvest time.
\n\n<b>5. Reduce Ice Cold Foods and Beverages</b>\n\n
The inner fire, known as agni, is the digestive power of the physical and energetic body. To stoke one’s inner fire, it is necessary to avoid dimming agni’s intensity with ice-cold foods and beverages. The agni of all doshas can become depleted if a steady stream of cold food or drinks is consumed. Vata and Kapha doshas, in particular, should lean toward warm foods and teas, while Pitta doshas may enjoy cool (but not frozen) beverages and foods. In this way, the digestive power will remain strong.
\n\n<b>6. Stop Eating Three Hours Before Bedtime</b>\n\n
During sleep, the body repairs, heals, and restores while the mind digests thoughts, emotions, and experiences from the day. If the body’s energy is diverted into physical digestion, the physical healing and mental digestive processes are halted. For this reason, Ayurveda medicine recommends that the last meal of the day be relatively light and completed three hours before bed to avoid this imbalance. In this way, the body’s prana is free to do its rest and repair work at the deepest levels during sleep.
    </string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
</resources>